<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Events on Mark Fest 2</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/</link><description>Recent content in Events on Mark Fest 2</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 19:15:49 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Charity Experts</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/charity-experts/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 13:50:44 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/charity-experts/</guid><description>Do you want to broadcast a charity you love, raise money for it, hear about some other charities, donate some money yourself, and feel great for donating money?!
Then compete in this contest! Or just come and watch!
Each participant will have 2 minute to sell the group on a charity they love. Then up to 3 minutes will be allowed for questions from the audience.
After all the charities have been presented, members will then actually donate what they are moved to donate.</description></item><item><title>Arctic Adventure</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/arctic-adventure/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 14:40:47 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/arctic-adventure/</guid><description>Want to experience social encouragement to experience cold water?!
Then come along on this artitic adventure!
I&amp;rsquo;ve been taking cold showers lately because they&amp;rsquo;re exhilerating and it feels good to warm up afterwards. Also there&amp;rsquo;s evidence that they are healthy!
At the start of this event we&amp;rsquo;ll get on discord to psych each other up, then we&amp;rsquo;ll break for 15 minutes for a cold shower, then rejoin to warm up and congratulate each other!</description></item><item><title>Spanish Scuba Divers</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/spanish-scuba-divers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 19:15:49 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/spanish-scuba-divers/</guid><description>Want to practice your Spanish?!
Then come dive into it with me!
For this event, we&amp;rsquo;ll practice multiple rounds of only speaking Spanish for 5 minutes with a 5 minute English break to ask questions.</description></item><item><title>Dancing Songs Altar</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/dancing-songs-altar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:06:29 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/dancing-songs-altar/</guid><description>Want to enjoy dancing to a playlist catered to me?! Want to get a prize for accurately predicting what I&amp;rsquo;ll like?!
Submit a Youtube link to a song that you think I&amp;rsquo;ll want to dance to here sometime before the start of Mark Fest. Then reach out to me to let me know you&amp;rsquo;re participating in this event.
I&amp;rsquo;ll then create a youtube playlist of all the links and share the link to it with all participants on a special Discord channel.</description></item><item><title>Vegan Feast Contest</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/vegan-feast-contest/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 13:53:32 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/vegan-feast-contest/</guid><description>Want to encourage yourself to eat more vegan things without breaking the bank?!
Then join this contest!
Each participant will make a vegan feast for themselves using less than $20 of ingredients (excluding spices). Plan your cooking so that you can comfortably jump in our Discord channel at 7pm and finish creating your feast by 8pm. We&amp;rsquo;ll then eat together!
I will declare winners in the following categories:
Fanciest Greatest Quantity Most Inventive Most Likely to be Made by Me</description></item><item><title>Sore Back Buddies</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/sore-back-buddies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 19:15:09 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/sore-back-buddies/</guid><description>Do you sometimes get a sore back and want some social encouragement to practice healthy back stretches?!
Then come and stretch with me!
We&amp;rsquo;ll all get on a spcial Discord channel and teach each other the stretches we know and practice them together.</description></item><item><title>Projection Party</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/projection-party/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 19:14:59 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/projection-party/</guid><description>Do you want to participate in a social experiment I invented?!
The setup is that I&amp;rsquo;ll write down some stuff I did recently and then read it out loud to the group - but in a flat tone so that I don&amp;rsquo;t reveal any of my attitudes about any detail.
In between statements, participants will be encouraged to respond in the format &amp;ldquo;that sounds [feeling word] (like &amp;ldquo;fun&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;disgusting&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;tedius&amp;rdquo;, etc.</description></item><item><title>Moving Songs Altar</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/moving-songs-altar/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 13:06:12 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/moving-songs-altar/</guid><description>Want to enjoy feeling connected to the universe through a playlist of moving songs catered to me?! Want to get a prize for accurately predicting what I&amp;rsquo;ll like?!
Submit a Youtube link to a piece of music that you think will move me here sometime before the start of Mark Fest. Then reach out to me to let me know you&amp;rsquo;re participating in this event.
I&amp;rsquo;ll then create a youtube playlist of all the links and share it with all participants on a special Discord channel.</description></item><item><title>Documentary Club</title><link>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/documentary-club/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 12:42:48 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://markjohnson4.github.io/markfest2/event/documentary-club/</guid><description>Want to learn some new stuff related to healing the planet and talk about it with others?!
Then watch the documentary &amp;ldquo;Super Fungi&amp;rdquo; (52 minutes) with me and let&amp;rsquo;s talk about it!
We&amp;rsquo;ll start the documentary through Amazon&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;watch together&amp;rdquo; option and then share our thoughts about it afterwards.</description></item></channel></rss>